VICTOR MANUEL

VELAZQUEZ FUENTES

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I'm a software engineer with a preference in frontend development. I like to participate in all stages of the creation of quality software and learn from those with more experience who can contribute something to my own professional and personal development.

CONTACT

- https://github.com/VictorMany
- victor.velazfuentez@gmail.com
- 4741034817
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/vi ctor-manuel-velazquezfuentes-bab088156/

EDUCATION

Universidad de la Salle Bajío |

Software engineering | 2018-2022

ABILITIES

GENERAL

- Good partner and capable of independent work
- Ease of following instructions and generating quality results
- Basic knowledge in Project Management
- Experience with agile methodologies (SCRUM)

LANGUAGES

English | Basic - Intermediate.

SKILLED TECH TOOLS

Development languages and frameworks

- Web application development with CSS, HTML and Javascript
- Knowledge of frameworks such as Vue JS, Quasar, Nuxt JS, Angular JS and React
- Database management with Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB and Firebase.

Platforms, services, programs

- Microsoft 365 (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)
- Visual Studio Code
- Visual Studio
- SQL Server Management Studio
- MySQL Workbench
- o Git
- Adobe XD
- Fiama
- Bootstrap
- Vuetify

RECOGNITIONS AND AWARDS

 I got a full scholarship for college tuition at the de La Salle Bajío University | 2018 - 2022

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

June 2020 - June 2021

León, Gto. (Remote)

Frontend development of WEB system in Quasar Framework.

It is a CMMS aimed at Biomedical Engineering departments to increase their productivity by helping to generate reports and maintenance for biomedical assets.

Software engineer intern at Valadevs

June 2021 - January 2022

León, Gto. (Hybrid)

- Full stack development and maintenance of Php projects
- Creation of interfaces and connection to MySQL
- Manipulation of MySQL databases

Frontend developer at Nextline

January 2022 - I currently work here

Guadalajara, Jalisco. (Remote)

- Work collaborating with agile SCRUM Methodology
- Frontend development with Vue JS framework
- API Usage
- Creation of views and interfaces